=The Forbidden Woman=
= المرأة المحرمة =
=Episode 5=
= الحلقة 5 =
Even if I'd forbidden you to eat it,
حتى لو منعتك من أكله ،
didn't you have a bite on the side?
ألم يكن لديك لدغة على الجانب؟
Besides,
بجانب،
the homecooked food is cleaner.
الطعام المطبوخ في المنزل أنظف.
I think
أظن
there's no contradiction for you to get pleasure
ليس هناك تناقض بالنسبة لك للحصول على المتعة
and be healthy.
وكن بصحة جيدة.
Dear.
عزيزي.
I...
أنا...
I didn't eat something behind your back.
لم آكل شيئًا خلف ظهرك.
I just don't want
أنا فقط لا أريد
to have you work too much.
أن تعمل كثيرا.
Well.
نحن سوف.
(Lingrui's Launching Event)
(حدث إطلاق Lingrui)
(Lingrui Group)
(مجموعة Lingrui)
Only one and a half months left before the company goes public.
لم يتبق سوى شهر ونصف قبل طرح الشركة للاكتتاب العام.
What's the solution you've been discussing this morning?
ما الحل الذي كنت تناقشه هذا الصباح؟
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
Calm down.
اهدأ.
We've contacted the affected customers.
لقد اتصلنا بالعملاء المتضررين.
We're in the middle of the negotiation.
نحن في منتصف المفاوضات.
Can the negotiation help in solving the problem for the company?
هل يمكن أن يساعد التفاوض في حل المشكلة للشركة؟
I hire you
أنا أوظفك
to solve the problem.
لحل المشكلة.
I have no time for you to try an error.
ليس لدي وقت لك لتجربة خطأ.
Cici.
سيسي.
What did the shareholders say?
ماذا قال المساهمون؟
The vice president manages to handle the shareholders for the time being.
نائب الرئيس يدير للتعامل مع المساهمين في الوقت الحاضر.
No news from Ruide yet?
لا يوجد أخبار من Ruide حتى الآن؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
Public Relations Department.
قسم العلاقات العامة.
What have you done?
ماذا فعلت؟
We've prepared an apology statement.
لقد أعددنا بيان اعتذار.
If we don't respond to this incident,
إذا لم نرد على هذا الحادث ،
the netizens and investors would reckon that our product is flawed.
يعتقد مستخدمو الإنترنت والمستثمرون أن منتجنا معيب.
In my opinion,
فى رايى،
we should apologise to them
يجب أن نعتذر لهم
and offer them some compensation
ونقدم لهم بعض التعويضات
to avoid them filing a lawsuit against us.
لتجنب رفع دعوى قضائية ضدنا.
No, don't apologise to them.
لا ، لا تعتذر لهم.
Before the judicial institute issues a formal test result
قبل أن يصدر المعهد القضائي نتيجة اختبار رسمية
and we have yet to get to the bottom of this,
وما زلنا بحاجة إلى الوصول إلى الجزء السفلي من هذا الأمر ،
it means we admit that our product is defective
هذا يعني أننا نعترف بأن منتجنا به عيب
if we offer apology and compensation.
إذا قدمنا ​​الاعتذار والتعويض.
The priority now is to investigate the case.
الأولوية الآن هي التحقيق في القضية.
Oh.
أوه.
I'm so sorry.
اسف جدا.
I hope I didn't disturb you.
آمل ألا أكون قد أزعجتك.
I overheard your conversation just now.
سمعت محادثتك للتو.
Get to the bottom of this as soon as possible.
نصل إلى الجزء السفلي من هذا في أقرب وقت ممكن.
Listen.
استمع.
Never leave the slightest blot on our company
لا تترك أبدًا أدنى وصمة عار على شركتنا
before the listing process is done.
قبل أن تتم عملية الإدراج.
Understood?
فهمت؟
Yes.
نعم.
Yes, Mr. Jiang.
نعم ، السيد جيانغ.
You may go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
What brings you here, dear?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا يا عزيزي؟
You have a business dinner tonight.
لديك عشاء عمل الليلة.
I bring you the chaser.
أحضر لك المطارد.
You're considerate, dear.
أنت متفهم يا عزيزي.
Don't frown.
لا تجهم.
You have many excellent staff under you.
لديك العديد من الموظفين الممتازين تحت قيادتك.
Don't bear the pressure all by yourself.
لا تتحمل الضغط وحدك.
I'm stressing out
أنا أؤكد
because of the listing procedure.
بسبب إجراءات الإدراج.
It's been five years.
لقد مرت خمس سنوات.
I know how much effort you've put in
أعرف مقدار الجهد الذي بذلته
since you obtained the first funding.
منذ حصولك على التمويل الأول.
Dear.
عزيزي.
The company survived in every plight
نجت الشركة في كل محنة
because of you.
بسببك.
You gave up
لقد استسلمت
on your career and ideal for my sake back then.
في حياتك المهنية ومثالية من أجلي في ذلك الوقت.
Do you regret it?
هل تندم علي هذا؟
What about you?
وماذا عنك؟
Would you start up the company again
هل ستبدأ الشركة مرة أخرى
if you knew the hardships you'd be going through in five years?
إذا كنت تعرف المصاعب التي ستمر بها في غضون خمس سنوات؟
Mr. Jiang.
السيد جيانغ.
You need to leave now.
أنت بحاجة إلى المغادرة الآن.
All right.
حسنا.
I'm off then.
أنا خارج بعد ذلك.
I'm going back home now.
سأعود إلى المنزل الآن.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Let me see you off.
دعني اراك
Dear.
عزيزي.
Get home safely.
الحصول على المنزل بأمان.
I'll go back now.
سأعود الآن.
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Go ahead.
إنطلق.
Yes.
نعم.
Executive Assistant Qin.
مساعد تنفيذي تشين.
(Mr. Jiang, I'm sorry to inform you)
(السيد جيانغ ، يؤسفني إبلاغك)
(that Mr. Gu can't attend the dinner tonight)
(أن السيد جو لا يمكنه حضور العشاء الليلة)
(as something comes up suddenly.)
(عندما يظهر شيء ما فجأة.)
This appointment was arranged a while ago.
تم ترتيب هذا الموعد منذ فترة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
(Cici)
(سيسي)
(Today's dinner is cancelled.)
(تم إلغاء عشاء اليوم).
(You don't have to come over.)
(ليس عليك القدوم.)
One shot of Godfather.
طلقة واحدة من العراب.
(Executive Assistant Qin)
(مساعد تنفيذي تشين)
(The subscriber you're calling is busy.)
(المساعد التنفيذي تشين) (المشترك الذي تتصل به مشغول.)
(Please try again later.)
(الرجاء معاودة المحاولة في وقت لاحق.)
French Connection.
وصلة فرنسية.
On the house.
على المنزل.
Perhaps a new flavour
ربما نكهة جديدة
will delight you.
سوف يسعدك.
Are you so generous
هل انت كريم جدا
to all customers?
لجميع العملاء؟
It depends on
هذا يعتمد على
(Bartender Yuan Xiao'ai) whether he's an Adonis to me.
(النادل Yuan Xiao'ai) ما إذا كان من Adonis بالنسبة لي.
One shot of Stinger for you.
طلقة واحدة من ستينغر لك.
It's on me.
دعه علي.
French Connection
وصلة فرنسية
is a great match for Hunter.
هي مباراة رائعة لهنتر.
Do you agree?
هل توافق؟
Good morning, Wei.
صباح الخير يا وي.
Do you have a sound sleep yesterday?
هل نمت عميقًا أمس؟
There's no one here.
لا يوجد أحد هنا.
Stop acting.
توقف عن التمثيل.
When are you going to divorce?
متى ستطلقين؟
Both of us know it very well.
كلانا يعرفه جيدًا.
No matter how hard you try,
بغض النظر عن مدى صعوبة محاولة،
Jiang Fengyan won't love you anymore.
لن أحبك جيانغ فنغيان بعد الآن.
Did Jiang Fengyan grant you a promise
هل منحك جيانغ فنغيان وعدًا
and go back on his word again?
ويعود عن كلمته مرة أخرى؟
Mind your own business.
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة.
Name a price.
اسم السعر.
Do you want me to file the divorce?
هل تريد مني رفع دعوى الطلاق؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Give me seventy million.
أعطني سبعين مليون.
I'll leave Jiang Fengyan immediately.
سأترك جيانغ فنغيان على الفور.
Seventy million?
سبعون مليون؟
Are you serious about this?
هل أنت جاد في هذا؟
Miss Xiang.
ملكة جمال شيانغ.
I'm serious about it if you offer the money.
أنا جاد في ذلك إذا عرضت المال.
Deal.
صفقة.
Heaven is watching you.
السماء تراقبك.
Aren't you afraid
ألا تخافين
you'd be exposed
سوف تتعرض
for what you did?
على ماذا فعلت
Regardless of the Xiang's property or Jiang Fengyan,
بغض النظر عن ممتلكات Xiang أو Jiang Fengyan ،
I'll claim back everything
سأطالب بإعادة كل شيء
that belongs to me.
ينتمي لي.
The torment on you
العذاب عليك
rejoices me the most.
يفرحني أكثر.
I wonder
انا اتعجب
when will Heaven
متى الجنة
seek justice for you.
اطلب العدالة من أجلك.
Don't you worry about me
لا تقلق علي
in this regard.
في هذا الصدد.
I'll be hearing from you.
سأسمع منك.
Meng.
منغ.
Sell my three-per-cent share.
بيع حصتي البالغة ثلاثة في المائة.
As soon as possible.
في أقرب وقت ممكن.
(Chu Group)
(مجموعة تشو)
Ms. Chu.
السيدة تشو.
We detected the movement of Xiang's family.
اكتشفنا حركة عائلة Xiang.
Don't talk in the middle of the game.
لا تتحدث في منتصف اللعبة.
Understood.
مفهوم.
Keep a close eye on Xiang Group.
ترقب عن كثب مجموعة Xiang.
Find a company with clean records
ابحث عن شركة ذات سجلات نظيفة
to buy the three per cent share.
لشراء حصة الثلاثة في المائة.
Yes.
نعم.
♪If you insist on leaving, I'll let you go♪
♪ إذا أصررت على المغادرة ، فسأطلق سراحك ♪
♪My love for you, I'll keep it♪
♪ حبي لك ، سأحتفظ به ♪
♪Encountering you in a different world♪
♪ مواجهتك في عالم مختلف ♪
♪I'm content♪
♪ أنا راضٍ ♪
♪With what I possessed before♪
بما كنت أملكه من قبل ♪
♪An unexpected love♪
♪ حب غير متوقع ♪
♪Is an abrupt blessing♪
هي نعمة فجائية
♪Regardless of whether your love is genuine or not♪
♪ بغض النظر عما إذا كان حبك حقيقي أم لا
♪Your place in my heart never changes♪
مكانتك في قلبي لا تتغير
♪Even if I have to be punished for falling for you♪
♪ حتى لو كان يجب أن أعاقب لوقوعك في حبك ♪
♪I'm not afraid of that♪
♪ لست خائفًا من ذلك ♪
♪Bring it on. I won't back down♪
اجلبه.  لن أتراجع ♪